And basically what this is, is a brief overview of what is going to be in the report.
Let's say someone doesn't have time to take a look at your whole report at this particular time, or maybe not even ever.
What would be the major points that you would want them to see and know that are in that report.
What would be the information, that could possibly peak their interest to further examine your report.
That is what is going to be on this page.
Now this is different than what we've written earlier in an earlier page, where we've, you know, talked about, this is why we wrote the report, these are the highlights of the report.
This is this is a little bit different.
This is think and terms of, if you had ten lines or less, ten sentences or less to tell me what this 10, 20, 30, 40 page report is about, do it.
And that's all it is.
It's not a full page, it's not three pages.
It's a paragraph.
Sum up in one paragraph what the highlights of this report are.